JoJo won his battle against that demon.
Poor Sod.
He lost everything in the process.
That's why I brought
him here three days ago.
And now, bereft of father and home alike,
how's he gonna muster up the will to live?
Don't give up on the world yet, JoJo!
In the sky, the two of the
stars were falling down.
The light and the darkness of the sky,
the light and the darkness of the sky.
The path of the path of the
path of the path Let's go.
Thank
you
so
much
for
watching.
Spirit!
That's what he needs, so
I'm gonna give it to him!
Huh?
It's the dead of night, but
there's a lamp burning in his room.
What do we have here?
How long's she been at it?
Don't tell me she's been
watching over him all this time.
Her fingers!
Cracked from the damp, I'd wager.
She must have been cooling his burns
round the clock for them to get like that.
Thank goodness.
He's awake.
You're through the worst of it.
You should be fine.
So you've been tending to my injuries.
But how can...
How can you be standing here?
You're the image of...
But no, I'm sorry.
Your face reminds me of
a girl I used to know.
Her name wouldn't happen to be...
Iran Pendleton, would it?
It's you!
It's been a long time, Jonathan Joestar.
Jojo.
Iran, you've really grown up? Me?
But you've grown a fair sight more.
Yet, you're still the boy you were.
Yeah.
She makes a better Florence
Nightingale than I do anyhow.
You rest up, Jojo!
Time for Speedwagon to make his exit?
I...
I must have fainted for a moment
But your arm!
It's broken, you shouldn't have caught me
You...
you caught me long ago.
I dare say old Jojo won't be lacking
a reason to live after this reunion.
You should have made an early
night of it, you hauled it.
Big mistake.
Most men shackle themselves
to petty morality.
They fear the consequences of their evil.
But some are unfettered by
man's laws in all their tyranny.
They are the vanguard.
Become my servant, Jack the Ripper.
You've no further need for free will.
I will make you an instrument of death,
the likes of which you can't
begin to imagine. Do it.
As for what I shall take in return...
Only Speedwagon and I know what
truly took place here that night.
Deer was consumed in the inferno,
but what of the accursed mask?
No sign of it in the rubble.
Smashed by falling masonry?
I hope so.
I want to put this
nightmare behind me. Jojo!
Arena!
That man, he haunts our steps.
Is something wrong?
No, all is well.
Ah, Signore Joestar.
And the lass at your side
is Signorina Pendleton.
Who are you?
You survived against the mask.
Not many men can claim that.
Jojo!
That's right.
Let the shock of that impact
push all the air from your body.
Jojo!
Why?
He was already hurt, you cad.
It's true I knocked the air out
of him, but he'll thank me for it.
My arm!
What is this?
My broken bones feel like they're mending!
Baron Zeppeli, at your service.
Courage alone will not be
enough to beat the mask.
My arm was shattered, but now...
The pain has subsided.
Lifting this rock is nothing.
That's incredible!
Sir, why are you here?
And what is happening to me?
Please, try to limit yourself
to one question at a time.
You healed yourself, Jojo.
How you breathed after
I poked you was the key.
But why did you go to the
trouble in the first place?
And how did you know who I...
He's gone.
What part of one question
at a time eluded you?
You'll get the answers you desire, Amico.
Follow me.
This day,
I will show you things the likes of
which will change your destiny forever.
It was with good reason that
I struck you in the diaphragm.
The shock of the impact
altered your breathing.
But how did that heal my arm?
With the energy I am about
to demonstrate for you.
Wait, what mischief is he planning?
Hrgh.
Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
Look at him, Arena!
His legs!
Those ripples!
I've never seen water do that!
What you see is the force that eased
your pain and healed your broken bones,
Senore Joestar! Ahhh!
Don't do it!
That frog seems none the worse.
That was Saint you saw.
Wait, Saint?
It's ripple energy created by Hamon.
I sent my Hamon coursing harmlessly
through Froggy to split my real target,
the rock below.
Jojo!
I know for a fact the stone
mask was not destroyed.
Dio Brando keeps it close to him even now.
No, it can't be!
Baron, is Dio still alive?
Indeed, and he holds the mask
I have sought for decades now.
That mask must be destroyed!
And its master must be reduced to ash!
It is your destiny to fight
for this righteous cause.
You will learn to wield,
Saint, or you will die.
The future of humanity
is at stake my destiny.
What is he talking about?
None of it makes any sense
arena
She's already suffered
enough at Dio's hands.
I can't drag her into this
Incredible.
It's blossoming he's passing the
spare hormone energy from his healed
arm into the branch and sending
it into bloom and But amazingly,
he doesn't even realize he's doing it.
This boy, he is a natural.
Of what might he be capable with the
proper refinement of his abilities?
Rejoice, mankind.
This day, I may have found your champion.
Hmm.
With every meal, I feel
my strength returning.
What a simple thing, the food chain.
As pigs feed on grass, so
does man feed upon them.
And I, at the top of it
all, feed upon the humans.
They exist to serve me
and quell my thirst.
Go, Jack.
It's supper time.
Now to swell the ranks of my
diabolical army and send it hence.
I will stand astride this world.
Humanity will kneel at Dio Brando's feet!
And so I began to study Harmon under
the tutelage of the mysterious Zeppeli.
The training was Spartan,
but I had no choice.
Here's how it came about.
Jojo, my history with the
Stone Mask has been a long one.
I was your age.
Hard to believe that
was ever the case now.
I harbored a great thirst for
adventure, as the young so often do.
It was my good fortune
to travel the world as
a member of my father's
archaeological team.
Would that we had never lain eyes
on those Aztec ruins that day.
You're saying?
Yes, the hands that pulled that evil artifact
into the light of day belonged to me.
One ill-fated night
during the voyage home,
a man of our number succumbed to
his curiosity and donned the mask.
The change in him was immediate.
Rampaging through the ship, he
ripped his companions' heads off?
in a bacchanalia of blood.
Fifty-eight crewmen, butchered
in a matter of minutes.
I dove into the sea to escape,
but the fiend gave chase.
Suddenly, dawn broke.
As he crumbled to dust in
the sunlight, I saw his face.
And to my utter horror,
the demon was my father.
The cruelest ship drifted away,
with the mask still aboard.
I had survived, but it was cold comfort.
Knowing the mask's dreadful
power could be unleashed again,
I dedicated my life to finding
a way to stop its evil.
That pledge led to my discovery of Hamon.
The energy we call Hamon is
created by the flow of one's blood.
Those who wear the mask feed on the
blood of others to consume that energy.
Hamon and the mask, they are
two sides of the same coin.
Of course, we can overload Dio with
that which animates him. Correct.
If we can hit Dio with enough Hamon
energy, that devil will burst asunder.
Homo's ripples are the same form as the
waves of light sent out by the sun itself,
the bane of all vampires.
Baron Zeppeli, I beg of you.
Teach me how to wield it.
I promise I'll give it my all.
You don't get a choice
in the matter, Amiko.
Given your contentious history with
Dio, I'm sure he will be coming for you.
There is a poetry to this, Jojo.
Breathing oxygenate your
blood your blood carries
the oxygen throughout your
body it enriches the cells
giving them the power to
keep on living those cells
combine to form you like
ripples in the water your body
thrums with the hormone
created by proper breathing
all that is left is to use
it there's no way he could
have reached me from there
how did he do that zoom
punch is a useful one I
merely dislocated my shoulder.
Harmon dulls the pain, and the
surprise is well worth the effort.
You must maintain the rhythm of
your breath, even when taking a hit.
If your mind or heart are tempestuous,
the caliber of your Harmon will suffer.
Yes, sir. Oi!
I found something!
Speedwagon!
Sir, the village is called
Wind Night's Lot. Right.
They've had a string of disappearances
lately, people vanishing after dark.
And folks have caught glimpses
of a Fool who looks like Dio.
We're out of time now.
Your final test will be one
of life or death, my pupil.
Yes, sir.
I'll meet him in combat and lay him low.
Give him hell!
Look, gents.
The entrance to Wyn Knight's lot.
We'll attack Dio while there's still
plenty of light left in the sky.
Arena, I left without giving
you a proper farewell.
Well, I swear, I will return to her!
Why did we stop? Oi, mate!
Hurry it up!
Keep an eye out.
Sunlight can't protect us in here.
Well, what's wrong?
Is it Dio?
That has to be him.
Listen, both of you.
Step away from the horses.
What in the blue hell?
That crazy blight is inside our horse!
Good God!
This one's mad as a hazard!
Dio's evil, yeah, but I ain't seen
him jump out of any animals so far.
He must be gathering minions, and
who knows how many he might have.
Stand aside, my young friends.
I will do the fighting.
He is a zombie.
They must feed on living flesh to survive.
However, they are in constant thrall to
their master, not unlike marionettes.
Oh, you lads are both as white as a sheep.
All the blood is drained from your faces.
Maybe I should cut off those useless heads
of yours and watch it
spray out of your necks!
Now, you melded corpses to
bay, prepare for the carnage!
Tell me, what's his next move?
You must think as he does.
Jojo, this strategy will
serve you in good stead.
Ask yourself, what would be the most
advantageous thing for my foe to do next?
Him, for example.
If he blocks off the tunnel entrance,
we can't retreat to the sunlight.
Just as I predicted,
he's blocked our retreat!
Speedwagon, jump!
Try harder.
Knives are coming out of him!
Baron Zeppeli!
You didn't say nothing
about fighting a pincushion!
Hamon Cutter!
I'm afraid your blades are rather
dull compared to my Hamon Cutter.
Jojo, this creature
illustrates a principle.
Imagine a minuscule flea, so
small that it's barely visible.
Why is it they bite
humans who tower over them
without a single thought
to their own safety?
Would you call their behavior courageous?
Of course not.
It's hunger compelling them.
I will tell you what courage is, Jojo.
Courage is to look your fear in the eye
and know that it has no dominion over you.
Fear scatters your breathing.
When you toss your fear into the dust,
breathing is the sword ever at your hip.
Breathe with courage and you
will never want for Hormone.
Bravery is our birth, white lads.
And for all the abilities
they may bring into a battle,
courage is something a zombie
relinquished when he took this form.
They're no better than peace.
There's no way here!
A knee full of hormone to the head seems
to have cured this one's braggadocio.
I don't believe it.
He didn't even spill any wine.
Jojo, you finish the creature off.
Destroy the brain.
It's the only way anything else
and you risk it coming back?
Time for the slaughter not me little pigs!
I'll cut you to shreds one by one.
Don't tell me we're following
him into that passageway.
It has to be destroyed,
but we will be doing no such
thing Jojo I I expect you to
finish off this abomination
without spilling a single drop.
All right, one last bit
of advice before you go.
There were no Vikings
in the land of Norway.
Until the north wind
blew in and created them.
If even one drop of
that vino goes to waste.
I don't care how utterly
you defeat the zombie.
I will abandon you here and now.
Boy, listen to yourself.
Have you gone insane?
I know what I'm doing.
I will do my best.
Like the Vikings, I will be
strengthened by hardship.
It's a labyrinth.
Even with this torch, all it's doing
is casting shadows to bedevil me.
The torch, I'm bright as day to him.
All this does is
illuminate my position but
without it I haven't a
clue where he's lurking?
Or from where he'll strike?
Even in the dark I can smell
the blood from his arm.
I must think like my foe,
just as the Baron commanded.
I'm sure he's close.
Next I must master my fear,
lest it sap my harm on.
Breathing is the sword at my hip.
That's it.
A little closer, and I'll be picking
my teeth with your bones, boy.
The harsh wind blowing down off of the
Arctic Ocean birthed the fearsome Vikings.
Only when we are tossed headlong into the
crucible of adversity do
we rise to the challenge.
What will a glass of
vino create this night?
If he should fail, Dio has already won.
What?
The wine is rippling.
Of course, just like when we
were training in the stream.
It's conducting the Hormone.
It passes through the glass, my
arm, my body, the ground itself.
I can feel his vibrations in the wine.
With Hormone, all is made clear to me now.
My spirit trembles.
My heart is ablaze.
I found you, zombie!
These stones offer no protection.
Send Dohom on overdrive!
Turn the corner so I can feast on you!
Sounds like you passed the
test with flying colors, Jojo.
Excellent.
Adversity has made the lad a Viking.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through
the sun and in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Cold in morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Miles come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
When my lover will be there.
And we'll see you?
This time I break you!
Curses on you, Queen!
Can he overcome this delusion?
A duel between heroes.
I'm ending your reign
of terror here and now!
Thank you.